ERIKA ZIBELNIK

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

INFO

ADDRESS

3180 Conservation Pl. Apt 201, Melbourne, 32934, United States

PHONE

4403829494

EMAIL

e.m.zibelnik@gmail.com

LINKS

Github

<u>LinkedIn</u>

SKILLS

HTML5

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

CSS3

• • 0 0 0

JavaScript

• • 0 0 0

jQuery

• • 0 0 0

Node.js

• • 0 0 0

Responsive Design

• • 0 0 0

Heroku

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

Git

• • 0 0 0

User Authentication

• • 0 0 0

PHP frameworks

• • 0 0 0

React.js

• • 0 0 0

MySQL

• • 0 0 0

Interpersonal Communication

• • • • •

PROFILE

I am interested in a challenging full stack developer opportunity in an environment where innovation, education, and creativity are valued. I have been passionate about development and will use the skills I learned with consideration of customer needs, functionality, latest technology, and programming standards. I have solid experience in previous places of work with troubleshooting and problem solving. I am a fast learner and strong team player with excellent social skills to interact with any individual.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Veterinary Technician, Rockledge Animal Clinic

Rockledge, Florida

Oct 2019 — Aug 2020

Blood draws, cytology for ear and urine, fecals, and more

Loading rooms, gathering patient information, providing prescriptions

Preparing patients for surgery and monitoring during surgery

I Holding animals for their safety and to protect the doctor or tech working on them

© Euthanasia

X-rays on dogs and cats

Placing catheters and starting IVs

Educating owners on parasites and lifestyle vaccines

Biologist, Enviroscience

Stow, Ohio

Jul 2019 — Sep 2019

species diversity

Snorkeling and scuba for collecting mussels in waterways

 ${\tt I\! Variety}\ of\ survey\ techniques\ with\ randomized\ sampling\ to\ determine\ quantity\ and$

Measuring, aging, identifying, and sexing mussels

I Identifying areas of interest with threatened and endangered mussel species

Outdoor Education, Footpath Foundation

Cleveland, Ohio

Mar 2019 — Sep 2019

If Guided nature hikes providing information about natural history with specific topics in

mind

Educating on native flora and fauna, habitats, conservation, preservation, watersheds,

other natural science related topics and more

I Incorporating school language and topics into programs

Interpersonal Skills

.

Ability to Work in a Team

.

Effective Communication

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet

Effective Team Leader

.

Adaptability

....

Hardworking

 \bullet

Adapting programs for various ages and levels of outdoor experience

Naturalist, Lake Metroparks

Kirtland, Ohio

Feb 2019 — Jun 2019

I Guided nature hikes providing information about natural history

Educating on native flora and fauna, habitats, conservation, preservation, watersheds,

other natural science related topics and more

Running children's camps of various ages

I Crafting educational programs, creating visual media, creating signage and more

I Training with permanent resident animals for various programs

Creating special hikes and family programs

Education Program Specialist, Lake Erie Nature andBay Village, Ohio **Science Center**

Jun 2018 — Jun 2019

Educate the public with a variety of programs from 1+ years of age

If Guided nature hikes providing information about the surroundings, plants, animals,

fungi and more

Educating on natural history and STEM field trips

Running children's camps of various ages

 $\ensuremath{\mathbb{I}}$ Crafting educational programs, creating visual media, creating signage and more

I Training with permanent resident animals for various programs

Seasonal Naturalist, Cleveland Metroparks

Willoughby, Ohio

Aug 2018 — Jan 2019

If Guided nature hikes providing information about the surroundings, plants, animals,

fungi and more

Educating on natural history

I Crafting educational programs, creating visual media, creating signage and more

I Training with permanent resident animals for various programs

I Care for permanent resident ambassadors: enclosure cleaning, diet preparation,

enrichment, training, and more

Creating special hikes and family programs

I Invasive plant ID and removal

EDUCATION

Associate of Science, Lakeland Community College

Kirtland, Ohio

Aug 2012 — May 2015

Undergraduate degree in biological sciences.

Bachelor's in Biology, Cleveland State University

Cleveland, Ohio

Aug 2015 — May 2018

Undergraduate in biological sciences, with a focus on conservation biology.

Certificate, National Association of Interpretation

Brecksville, Ohio

Mar 2019 — Mar 2019

Certified interpretive guides through NAI learn how to create programs for people of all ages and abilities.

Certificate, University of Central Florida

Oviedo, Florida

Aug 2020 — Nov 2020

This program enabled us to become full stack programers that learned:

- · HTML5
- · CSS3
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- Node.js
- · Responsive Design
- Heroku
- · Git
- · User Authentication
- · PHP frameworks like Laravel
- · React.js
- · MySQL